Friends welcome to Creative Money
Multiplier, in this video we will talk
about Lombard General Insurance and the
result of the Left Party. The
total
income generated in the result is Rs. 2018.
Complete it as per the fasting period of 2018, for
selling them for their water and air junior
both have been raised. Friends, if we talk about profit after
tax, it is
Rs. 376.4 crore in March 2018,
Rs. 80 crore in December 2018 and Rs. 3.5 crore in
March 2018, if we compare it with March 2018, then
this profit has decreased.
Friends, if we talk about profit after
tax here, then it is Rs. 21.83 crore,
complete it is Rs. 4.1 crore
and Rs. 220 to
Rs. 200 crore of March 2018, if we
compare it with March 2018, then this
is the rise in MS Word December  If we compare it with 2018, then
it has not happened, friends, if we
talk about the operating performance here
in billion rupees, then here you can see that
we have discussed that the profit after
tax has increased by 1.3 percent, making it
23.8 percent
and the profit before tax for the whole year
is that growth by 6.2%,
according to which the profit after tax has increased
by 30.8 percent, so
friends, if you come back here and look at it,
you can see that above f22 meeting
Pattha Oil and Combined Wishes and Rs
14.51 friends, according to this, the viral has been
maintained well, the entertainment condition is also and
friends, if you have not subscribed here, then
subscribe to Create Your Money Multiplayer in key
notifications, medicinal notifications and
new video uploads, friends, if we
talk about its price here, then its current
price is 108 times rupees, its 52-week low has
drawn in rupees and if
you look at the price chart here, then here below
It had increased to 100, it has
control, it belonged to 100,
after that it should come back regularly, it has gone to 3004 and is
resonating in a good price range and it is
a good insurance company and it will have to pay
20% in the future, so its impact
on the market is also 4 crore rupees and
its industry is 56.8, its price to
cases 147 friends, voice of the
railway station is quite good and right now
due to the impact of midnight in it, there may be some downfall, the
auto industry is down and for the last two
months the entire business in the country is also stalled,
but whatever else is not renewal,
it all continues and there is Indian premium, so that much
interest will not come,
but still there is a chance of coming on some important news,
but that role is a good
moment in it and don't on the phone,
whenever the price goes to 100 on correction and there is an
opportunity to invest, long term
investors should invest in these minutes, so
friends, this was my video  On such general
Robert Pattinson insurance if you liked it
please like thank you very much
happiness team